=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 23=
=الخاطبة الحمراء الصغيرة= =الحلقة 23=
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل غارق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪
You did well.
لقد أبليت حسنا.
I'll achieve success soon as well.
سأحقق النجاح قريبًا أيضًا.
No matter how deep the bond between Tian Xi and Hong Luan is,
بغض النظر عن مدى عمق الرابطة بين تيان شي وهونغ لوان،
they can't break the Heartless Curse.
لا يمكنهم كسر لعنة القلب.
As it was made from Hong Luan's lost soul and spirit,
لأنه مصنوع من روح وروح هونغ لوان المفقودة،
only her tears can break it.
فقط دموعها يمكن أن تكسرها.
But without a soul and a spirit,
ولكن من دون روح وروح،
her ability to love is damaged
لقد تضررت قدرتها على الحب
and she can never cry tears.
ولا يمكنها البكاء أبدًا.
So, it is an invincible curse.
إذن فهي لعنة لا تقهر.
Sister, you're indeed awesome.
أختي أنت فعلا رائعة
You have successfully destroyed the marital tie between them,
لقد نجحت في تدمير الرابطة الزوجية بينهما،
so they can never return to their immortal places.
حتى لا يتمكنوا أبدًا من العودة إلى أماكنهم الخالدة.
I will be unstoppable.
سوف أكون لا يمكن وقفها.
It's been five hundred years.
لقد مرت خمسمائة سنة.
I can be free finally.
يمكنني أن أكون حراً أخيراً.
Xiaojiu,
شياوجيو,
once I turn the mortal world into a ruthless one,
بمجرد أن أحول العالم الفاني إلى عالم لا يرحم،
we can unite again.
يمكننا أن نتحد مرة أخرى.
Then the mortal world will be ours.
ثم العالم الفاني سيكون لنا.
- Moonlight scatters before my bed.
- ضوء القمر ينثر أمام سريري.  - ضوء القمر ينثر أمام سريري.
Did I teach you like this?
هل علمتك هكذا؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Can't you be serious?
ألا يمكنك أن تكون جاداً؟
Say that again.
قل ذلك مجددا.
(If I get drunk,)
(إذا سكرت)
(my heart won't hurt so much.)
(قلبي لن يؤلمني كثيرا.)
Stop drinking, please.
توقف عن الشرب، من فضلك.
The nine-tailed fox has broken the seal,
لقد كسر الثعلب ذو الذيول التسعة الختم،
and you're going to lose your job.
وسوف تفقد وظيفتك.
What's the point of being a fairy?
ما الفائدة من كونك خرافية؟
I can't save my beloved one,
لا أستطيع إنقاذ حبيبتي
nor can I save the common folk.
ولا أستطيع إنقاذ عامة الناس.
Is there really no other way?
هل حقا لا توجد طريقة أخرى؟
In fact,
في الحقيقة،
you are the Hong Luan.
أنت هونغ لوان.
Once Tian Xi and you get married,
بمجرد زواجك أنت وتيان شي،
you can return to your places.
يمكنكم العودة إلى أماكنكم.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
لماذا لم تخبرني في وقت سابق؟
It won't give us any help.
لن يقدم لنا أي مساعدة.
You've lost a soul and a spirit.
لقد فقدت روحًا وروحًا.
You can't even remember who you are.
لا يمكنك حتى أن تتذكر من أنت.
How can you do it?
كيف يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك؟
Over the years,
على مر السنين،
(I've been searching for your soul and spirit.)
(لقد كنت أبحث عن روحك وروحك.)
(Five hundred years ago,)
(قبل خمسمائة عام)
(the fragments have drifted here.)
(لقد انجرفت الشظايا هنا.)
(I used magic to turn you into a matchmaker.)
(لقد استخدمت السحر لتحويلك إلى الخاطبة.)
(But you can't even recall who you are.)
(لكنك لا تستطيع حتى أن تتذكر من أنت).
(It must be in the battle)
(يجب أن يكون في المعركة)
(that your ability to love was damaged.)
(أن قدرتك على الحب تضررت.)
Could there really be no ways to break the Heartless Curse
هل يمكن حقًا ألا تكون هناك طرق لكسر لعنة القلب
or defeat the nine-tailed fox?
أو هزيمة الثعلب ذو الذيول التسعة؟
There's still a way out.
لا يزال هناك طريقة للخروج.
(Great Doctor with Utmost Sincerity) The couple bow to each other.
(طبيب عظيم بإخلاص شديد) ينحني الزوجان لبعضهما البعض.
Let go of my master.
اترك سيدي.
He will not marry you.
لن يتزوجك.
It's not up to you.
انها ليست متروك لكم.
You should ask first,
عليك أن تسأل أولاً،
whether he still remembers who you are.
ما إذا كان لا يزال يتذكر من أنت.
Master, come with me.
معلمي، تعال معي.
I don't know you.
أنا لا أعرفك.
Changqing and I are the perfect match.
أنا و(تشانغتشينغ) نتوافق تمامًا.
You'll never break the Heartless Curse.
لن تكسر أبدًا لعنة القلب.
The Heartless Curse
لعنة بلا قلب
is created by your soul and spirit.
تم إنشاؤه من روحك وروحك.
Only your tears can break it.
وحدها دموعك يمكنها كسرها.
But you have lost them,
لكنك فقدتهم
so you'll never be able to shed tears.
لذلك لن تتمكن أبدًا من ذرف الدموع.
How can you break it?
كيف يمكنك كسرها؟
What's more,
ما هو أكثر من ذلك،
the world will soon be mine.
العالم سيكون لي قريباً.
Liu Yingying,
ليو ينجينج,
you lose.
تخسر.
Master, come with me.
معلمي، تعال معي.
You want to ruin my plan again.
تريد إفساد خطتي مرة أخرى.
Today I'll make you dead without tombs.
اليوم سأجعلكم أمواتاً بلا قبور.
The nine tails unite.
الذيول التسعة تتحد.
Mission accomplished.
تمت المهمة.
You're just struggling desperately.
أنت فقط تكافح بشدة.
(To be continued) You remember it now?
(يتبع) هل تتذكرينه الآن؟
Time's up for you.
لقد حان الوقت بالنسبة لك.
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل غارق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪